Saints and Soldiers: The Void is a war film directed by Ryan Little.
Germany, May 1945, deep in the Harz Mountains a U.S.
tank crew discovers a platoon of Germans preparing to ambush U.S.
supply trucks.
Cpl. Carey Simms, played by Adam Gregory.
Atwood, played by Tim Shoemaker.
Goss, played by Ben Urie.
Mitchell, played by Michael Todd Behrens.
Shonbeck, played by David Morgan.
Pvt. Nelson, played by Brenden Whitney.
Saints and Soldiers: The Void (also known as Saints and Soldiers: Battle of the
Tanks), is a 2014 war drama film directed and written by Ryan Little.
It serves as the third installment in the Saints and Soldiers film series, and
is a standalone sequel to Saints and Soldiers: Airborne Creed.
The film stars K.
Danor Gerald, Adam Gregory, and Matt Meese.
The Void was the most expensive of the Saints and
Soldiers films due to its use of tanks.
It was filmed in Alpine, Utah.
The film received mixed reviews with some critics calling it a "riveting drama" and some critics
stating that more focus on writing and execution would have improved the film.
The tone is thought_provoking.